Sharon Abramovich

Full Stack Developer

Petach Tikva | 050-9410940 | <u>abra.sharon@gmail.com</u> <u>github.com/SharonAbra</u> | <u>linkedin.com/in/sharonabramovich/</u> | <u>Portfolio</u>

SUMMARY

Full Stack Developer experienced in JavaScript based programming with a passion for building practical, beautiful and well-performing applications. Enjoys the process of planning, creating and finding elegant solutions. Has strong skills in problem solving, visual thinking and teamwork. Sociable, organized, and drives for the best results.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages: JavaScript (ES6)

Front-End: React.js, Redux, Bootstrap, HTML5, CSS3 Back-End: PostgreSQL, JSON Web Token, Node.js

Software: Git, Github

Development Practices: REST API design, Agile, Web App Architecture (MVC)

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Memory Game - Github | Demo

A full stack educational multi-player game to enrich English vocabulary.

- Designed a beautiful and clean user interface with React.js, including state management with redux.
- Facilitated an efficient node is server to handle data fetching and socket connection.
- Implemented a PostgreSQL database as the basis for the game's vocabulary.

BuudyBot - Github | Demo

A full stack chatbot app for entertainment and conversation.

- Created an extensive database of triggers and responses using PostgreSQL.
- Developed a node.js server to handle inputs and filter responses.
- Incorporated media from various APIs to make the app enriched and interactive.

EXPERIENCE

Program Director - International MA program

Tel Aviv, Israel 2013 - 2021

Tel Aviv University

- Implemented a formal education program by forecasting requirements, and verified its success.
- Devised corrective actions to course modules, to ensure the highest quality experience for the customers.
- Produced events and activities along with a team of coordinators, and responded to issues in real-time.

Administrative Director

IES Medical

Tel Aviv, Israel
2010-2011

• Managed the foreign residents department and verified that policies are issued guickly and accurately.

Facilitated efficient customer support services to achieve maximum client satisfaction.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development, Python and JavaScript program

Developers Institute, TLV Coding Bootcamp

Tel Aviv, Israel 06/2021 -12/2021

BA: Double Major - Psychology and Philosophy

Tel Aviv University

Tel Aviv, Israel 2010 - 2013

LANGUAGES

Hebrew - native speaker, English - fluent